Guide to the H.N. Tiemann & Co. Photograph Collection [1880-1916] PR 129
New-York Historical Society
- unspecified
  - Stock Exchange [Curb brokers (?), copy negative of a photograph by an unidentified photographer, 1892], undated (Box 8, Folder 363)
  - [Herald Square, copy negative of a photograph by an unidentified photographer, 1863], undated (Box 8, Folder 367)
  - [Broadway looking north from 37th Street], undated (Box 8, Folder 369)
  - [Greeley Square, Broadway, looking north from 32nd Street, showing the New York Herald Building], undated (Box 8, Folder 370)
  - [Broadway, looking south from Cedar Street], undated (Box 8, Folder 371)
  - [Broadway, looking north from Bowling Green], undated (Box 8, Folder 373)
  - [30th Street, looking east from Fifth to Madison Avenue], [1905] (Box 8, Folder 374)
  - [Man on early elevated railroad, possibly Charles T. Harvey, copy negative of a photograph by an unidentified photographer, 1867], undated (Box 8, Folder 375)
  - [Grand Circle], [1900] (Box 8, Folder 376)
  - [Blackwell's Island Penitentiary], undated (Box 8, Folder 379)
  - [Ruins of the Fayerweather & Ladew Factory, Allen and East Houston Streets, after an explosion and fire], 1903 Jan. (Box 8, Folder 380)
  - [Ruins of the Fayerweather & Ladew Factory, Allen and East Houston Streets, after an explosion and fire], 1903 Jan. (Box 8, Folder 381)
  - [Federal Hall], undated (Box 8, Folder 382)
  - [Interior of unidentified church], undated (Box 8, Folder 383)
  - State Camp of Instruction, Peekskill, N.Y., Company "E" Seventh Regiment, 1893 (Box 8, Folder 384)
  - [Presbyterian Church, 11th Street between Sixth and Seventh Avenues], [1916] (Box 8, Folder 385)
  - View in Fourth Avenue, N.Y. [Copy negative of a lithograph by Geo. Hayward, published in Valentine's Manual, 1861], undated (Box 8, Folder 386)
  - Hotel Waldorf, N.Y. [Copy negative of photograph by J.S. Johnston, 1893], undated (Box 8, Folder 388)
  - [Queensboro Bridge, from Queens Plaza], undated (Box 8, Folder 389)
  - [West 141st Street, Washington Heights], undated (Box 8, Folder 390)
  - [Croton Reservoir, showing a policeman standing in winter], undated (Box 8, Folder 391)
  - [Hall of Records], undated (Box 8, Folder 392)
  - [13-19 Broadway], undated (Box 8, Folder 393)
  - [Fifth Avenue at the corner of 40th Street], undated (Box 8, Folder 395)
  - [Shops and omnibus on lower Broadway], undated (Box 9, Folder 397)
  - [Croton Reservoir, demolition], [1900-1901] (Box 9, Folder 398)
  - The Ruins of Phelps & Pecks Store [Copy negative of a lithograph by Clay?], undated (Box 9, Folder 400)
  - [42nd Street, looking east from Madison Avenue, copy negative after a photograph by an unidentified photographer, ca. 1880s], undated (Box 9, Folder 403)
  - [Houses on Fifth Avenue?], undated (Box 9, Folder 406)
  - [Clinton Hall, Astor Place and 8th Street, copy negative after a photograph by Joseph Hall], undated (Box 9, Folder 408)
  - Broadway at the corner of Rector Street [Copy negative of a photograph by by an unidentified photographer], undated (Box 9, Folder 410)
  - [Broadway, looking north from 33rd Street, copy negative of a photograph by an unidentified photographer, ca. 1880s], undated (Box 9, Folder 411)
  - [Croton Reservoir, demolition], [1899-1901] (Box 9, Folder 412)
  - St. Thomas' Church, Fifth Avenue north of 52nd Street [Copy negative of a photograph by A. Wittemann, 1890], undated (Box 9, Folder 414)
  - [Second Avenue at the corner of 17th Street, showing St. Mark's Hospital], undated (Box 9, Folder 418)
  - [Fifth Avenue and 30th Street, southeast corner], [1915] (Box 9, Folder 420)
  - [New York Herald Building, copy negative of a photograph by an unidentified photographer], undated (Box 9, Folder 422)
  - [N.Y. Staats-Zeitung Building, Park Row, copy negative of a photograph by an unidentified photographer], undated (Box 9, Folder 424)
  - [Ruins of the Fayerweather & Ladew Factory, Allen and East Houston Streets, after an explosion and fire], 1903 Jan. (Box 9, Folder 425)
  - [Country Jail, 70 Ludlow Street], undated (Box 9, Folder 426)
  - [U.S. Capitol, Washington, D.C., copy negative of a photograph by an unidentified photographer], undated (Box 9, Folder 427)
  - Hotel Windsor [Copy negative of a photograph of J.S. Johnston, 1894], undated (Box 9, Folder 428)
  - N.Y.C. Freight Station, Hudson Street, undated (Box 9, Folder 429)
  - [Eden Museum], [1915] (Box 9, Folder 431)
  - [Essex Market Police Court], undated (Box 9, Folder 432)
  - [Portrait of unidentified man, negative of a painting by an unidentified artist], undated (Box 9, Folder 433)
  - [St. Thomas Church, Fifth Avenue and 53rd Street], [1915] (Box 9, Folder 434)
  - [Fifth Avenue between 43rd and 44th Streets], [1915] (Box 9, Folder 435)
  - Seventh Regiment Team, Creedmoor, Long Island, N.Y., 1896 (Box 9, Folder 436)
  - [Gilsey House, Broadway and 29th Street], undated (Box 9, Folder 437)
  - [East 27th Street, showing the Eglise St. Esprit], [1916] (Box 9, Folder 438)
  - [Queensboro Bridge, from Queen's Plaza], [1909] (Box 9, Folder 439)
  - [Broadway, looking south from 36th Street], 1905 (Box 10, Folder 442)
  - [Union Square East, view of a parade], undated (Box 10, Folder 443)
  - [Unidentified residence with people sitting on the porch], undated (Box 10, Folder 444)
  - Broad Street During the Panic [Copy negative of a wood engraving published in an illustrated newspaper, 1896], undated (Box 10, Folder 446)
  - [St. Paul's Chapel, copy negative of a print], undated (Box 10, Folder 447)
  - [Clinton Hall, Astor Place and 8th Street, copy negative of a photograph by an unidentified photographer], undated (Box 10, Folder 448)
  - [United Bank Building, Wall Street and Broadway, copy negative of a photograph by an unidentified photographer], undated (Box 10, Folder 449)
  - [Union Square West, copy negative of a photograph by an unidentified photographer, ca. 1879], undated (Box 10, Folder 451)
  - N.Y. House of Refuge [Copy negative of a lithograph by G. Hayward, 1832], undated (Box 10, Folder 453)
  - [34th Street looking east from Fifth Avenue, copy negative of a photograph by an unidentified photographer], undated (Box 10, Folder 454)
  - [Rooftop view of East 42nd Street, showing Holy Trinity Church and Grand Central Station, copy negative of a photograph by Snook], undated (Box 10, Folder 455)
  - [Parade, unidentified location, copy negative of a photograph by an unidentified photographer], undated (Box 10, Folder 456)
  - [42nd Street, looking west from Fifth Avenue, showing the Croton Reservoir and the elevated railway, copy negative of a photograph by American Photo Service, Inc.?], undated (Box 10, Folder 457)
  - [Shanties, copy negative of a photograph by an unidentified photographer], undated (Box 10, Folder 462)
  - [Seventh Regiment Armory, Park Avenue and 66-67th Streets], 1894 (Box 10, Folder 465)
  - Morning Ground Mount, State Camp, Peekskill, N.Y., 1897 (Box 10, Folder 469)
  - [Admiral Farragut Statue, Madison Square], undated (Box 10, Folder 470)
  - [St. John's Square, copy negative of a photograph by an unidentified photographer], undated (Box 10, Folder 471)
  - [23rd Street view of Flatiron Building from north side of Fifth Avenue, copy negative of a photograph by an unidentified photographer], undated (Box 10, Folder a)
  - ["Clermont" ship], undated (Box 10, Folder b)
  - [Hotel Wellington, corner missing from negative; beginning of original number 3? is visible], undated (Box 10, Folder c)
  - Emmanuel Synagogue [Temple Emanu-El, 1 East 65th Street], 1897 (Box 10, Folder d)